http://www.astrogallery.com/pages/privacy-policy

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Astro Gallery of Gems, recognizes and respects the importance of maintaining the privacy of our customers, registered members (&quot;Members&quot;) and users, and has established this Privacy Policy as a result. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform you of: • the personal information we may collect from you when you visit our web site, respond to ouremails, place orders via mail or fax, or otherwise contact us via telephone, email, fax or mail, use ourmobile applications, place orders through social media applications (such as our Facebook andInstagram) or otherwise contact us via telephone, email, fax or mail (collectively, our “Services”),• why we gather information from you,• how we collect it,• how we use it, and• the choices you have regarding our use of personal information you have provided.This Privacy Policy governs your use of our web site located at www.AstroGallery.com.  TheServices are owned by Astro Gallery of Gems, Inc. (the &quot;Company&quot;).Note: You must be 18 years or older and the age of majority in your place of residence to use,subscribe or register as a member of Astro Gallery of Gems (or 21 years or older). The Service is ageneral audience site and we do not knowingly collect, maintain or disclose personal informationfrom or about children under 13 years of age.Why do we gather information?Astro Gallery of Gems gathers personal information to help improve our products and customerservice, to communicate with you, to process your orders, to provide an enhanced and morepersonalized shopping experience and to inform you, and your gift and message recipients, ofspecial offers and discounts from us, our affiliated brands and selected third parties. What information do we gather?We collect information through our Web Site, emails, mail, fax, and telephone, mobile applicationsand social media applications (such as our Facebook Page) including when you:• place an order,• participate in our forums, surveys, contests, sweepstakes, promotions, content submissions, chats,bulletin boards, discussion groups, requests for suggestions, and membership registrations, and• engage in other activities, services, products and resources we make accessible to our customers,members or users.Depending on how you interact with us, we collect some or all of the following types ofinformation:• your name, address, telephone number, email address,• billing information (credit card number, expiration date alternate or additional billing information andbilling address),• products purchased and occasion type (for example, Valentine&#39;s Day),• any promotion or gift card code and related,• Message and gift recipients&#39; names, addresses, telephone numbers and email addresses, and• other information you provide to us, including User Submissions.Information you provide to us may be collected by us even if an order, registration, or other processis started but not completed or otherwise cancelled.How we use &quot;Cookies&quot; and &quot;Action Tags&quot;?A &quot;cookie&quot; is a small data file sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer.We use cookies to let us know that you are a prior customer, user or Member and to provide certainfeatures to you. Most web browsers allow you to instruct the browser to prevent the use of cookies.However, if you disable this feature, certain aspects of the Astro Gallery of Gems Web Site, such asthe shopping basket, may not function properly.We have relationships with third parties who may receive non-personal information directly from thecookies placed by our Web Site on your computer to assist in analyzing our business andcustomers.Our Web Site also uses a common web technology called &quot;action tags&quot; (also called single pixel gifsor web beacons) to anonymously track purchase, usage and other web activity information. Actiontags (including third party tags) may be used to provide data to third parties for tracking purposes.However, our Web Site does not use action tags to collect or transfer personal information.How we use the information we collect?We use information we collect to communicate with you, to process your orders, to provide anenhanced and more personalized shopping experience, to inform you and your gift and messagerecipients of offers and discounts from Astro Gallery of Gems and our affiliated brands and to enableyou to receive credits for purchases under loyalty or buying programs which you have joined.Our Affiliates, subcontractors, and agents, and any successors to our business (if we ever sell someor all of our business), are not considered to be third parties under this Policy. We may provide yourinformation to our Affiliates for use in connection with their businesses, including sending you offersand promotions. However, in connection with information collected under this Policy, they arerequired to comply with this Policy. &quot;Affiliates&quot; are persons or entities directly or indirectly controlling,controlled by, or under common control with Astro Gallery of Gems Inc.We may combine information we receive from you via our Services with information from ourAffiliates and third parties. We use the combined information to enhance and personalize yourshopping experience with us and to communicate with you in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We reserve the right to disclose information you provide to us as required by law, in response tolegal process and law enforcement requests and as necessary or appropriate, in our view, tooperate the Services, process orders or registrations, to conduct promotions, contests, andsweepstakes you participate in, and to protect the rights or property of the Company, its Affiliates,users, customers, recipients, Members, Sponsors, Providers, Licensors, Merchants and Associates.Please note that any personal information you reveal or post on one our public forums suchas a message board, chat room, discussion group, folder, survey, contest, sweepstakes, userreview and rate forum, and all User Submissions, are not protected by this Privacy Policy andmay be collected, shared and used by us or with third parties, including to contact you.Information you give out or post on our public forums you disclose at your own risk. Consent to Transfer and SubmissionOur Services are operated in the United States. If you are located outside the United States, pleasebe aware that any information you provide to us will be transferred to and stored in the UnitedStates. By using the Services or otherwise providing us with information, you hereby consent to thistransfer. Although personal information collected by us through our Services is used by us in accordance withthis Privacy Policy, laws generally applicable to the protection of personal data in the U.S. may notbe as stringent as those in other countries. Links to Other Web SitesAstro Gallery of Gems wants you to be aware that when you click on links and/or ad banners thattake you to affiliated or third-party web sites, or when you interact with us through third partyservices such as on our Facebook page, you will be subject to the privacy policies and terms of useof those services, not ours. We encourage you to read the posted privacy statement and user termswhenever using, and prior to providing any personal information to, any other service.Security and PasswordsIf you place an order on our Web site, it encrypts the credit card number you submit prior totransmission over the Internet using secure socket layer (SSL) encryption technology. Thistechnology works best when the Web Site is viewed using Microsoft&#39;s Internet Explorer® orNetscape Navigator®. However, no transmission of data over the Internet or any other network canbe guaranteed to be 100% secure. Although we make reasonable efforts to safeguard personalinformation once we receive it, we cannot warrant the security of information we receive.Portions of the Web Site (such as our Member registration and Address Book) may requireregistration and log-in processes in which you will select a user ID and password (collectively, the&quot;Password&quot;). Passwords provided to you by us are the confidential property of the Company andmay be used by you solely for your individual use of the Web Site (and otherwise as specified byus). You are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of any Password and for all activities thatoccur using your Password, whether or not authorized by you. You agree to immediately notify us ofany unauthorized use of your Password or accounts.We may provide you with the ability to log into our Services using a social media account, such asFacebook Connect. We do not control the activities of such social media services and have nocontrol over the data they collect or their privacy practices. You should review their privacy practicesbefore using any such social media service.How to Limit the Use of Personal InformationFrom Third PartiesWe do not share email addresses you provide with third parties without your consent. In addition, ifyou prefer that other personal information provided by you not be shared with third parties, please letus know by emailing, writing or calling us as described below. Your instructions will be processed assoon as reasonably practicable and in accordance with law.Emailing us at: info@astrogallery.com from the email address which you wish to have removed (i.e.not shared with third parties), and include your postal mailing address in the message; orWriting us at:   Astro Gallery of Gems Customer Satisfaction Department417 Fifth AvenueNew York, NY 10016Telephoning us at: 212-889-9000 Monday – Sunday, 10am to 6pm ET.From Astro Gallery of Gems If you also prefer that we not use the personal information you have provided to contact you or yourmessage or gift recipients for our own marketing and promotional purposes, please indicate in youremail or letter that you wish your instructions to apply to &quot;Astro Gallery of Gems&quot;. These instructions,however, do not apply to non-promotional messages from us.Any promotional email we send to you or your gift or message recipients will include a link to use toopt-out of receiving further promotional emails from the sender. Your Consent and Changes to this PolicySubject to the above provisions, by using our Web Site, you consent to the terms of this PrivacyPolicy. We may change our Privacy Policy from time to time as new features or services are added,suggestions from our customers are incorporated or other changes are made. We will post therevised Privacy Policy on our Web Site at least 30 days prior to their effective date - unless webelieve changes must take effect sooner to comply with law or to protect the Company or ourcustomers, users, Members, recipients, Sponsors, Providers, Licensors, Merchants, Associates andAffiliates, in which case the changes will be effective upon posting or as otherwise specified. By using AstroGallery.com, you agree to be legally bound and to abide by the Privacy Policy. Your CommentsAstro Gallery of Gems welcomes feedback concerning this Privacy Policy. Please send yourcomments and questions to: info@astrogallery.com
